[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
-Someone stood out to me.
-Who?
That Rahmboy.
Be careful.
Especially around Agent Alex.
Nothing changes in the plan.
We're going through with it.
Oh, and Chiara asked me
to give this to you.
I'm really getting stressed out
because of that GAGO.
I don't want them to be
the only ones having fun.
But seriously.
I really thought
you wouldn't be able to make it
to my wedding.
She's so beautiful, Viktor. Look at her.
This means so much to me, having you here.
This might just be the best wedding gift
I could ask for.
Don't ruin my makeup.
Actually, we should be the ones
thanking you.
Didn't you tell me before
that everything is possible?
Because of all your sacrifices,
for staying with the agency,
Your sacrifices were definitely worth it,
even with the case your father and I have.
It's okay because they understood
that we're your parents.
then why are you still hurt?
Don't worry.
I knew he wasn't really
a true public servant.
Calm down.
It's your wedding. Don't stress.
-Don't stress, okay?
-Yes.
I feel so bad
that there's nothing I can do.
Don't, daughter.
We'll handle it, please.
Just focus on being happy.
We're here to celebrate!
Yay!
-Thank you!
-I’m getting married!
Mama Yaya? You mean,
La Morte Bianca's Mama Yaya?
Your nanny when you trained in Sicily?
What is she doing here?
She's from Albay too?
And she just happens
to show up for your wedding?
How's Vicky?
What's her plan here?
Well, whatever Mama Yaya's plan is,
that's for her to decide.
If there's anything
I've learned all these years,
Even when it's difficult.
Even when it's complicated.
And even when the situation
is sometimes frightening.
But when you love someone,
you have to be wholehearted
and sincere in your intentions.
That the decision you make
is for the good of the people you love.
Love wears many faces.
There are many ways to care
and many ways to sacrifice.
But why do we always have to choose?
There's always a decision to make.
And when we make our decisions,
we try to choose what's right.
We try to do everything we can
to make things right.
And until the very end,
I will choose to love in the only way
I know how.
For the person I love most.
Mr. Mikoy Pinagpala, I will marry you.
And I will stay by your side
until my very last breath.
MJ.
Why is it taking so long
for the door to open?
MJ?
MJ.
Why is the bride taking so long?
Agent Alex is running?
Where's Chiara?
Why hasn't she come out yet?
I don't know either.
Maybe there was just a small problem?
It can't be a small problem.
Let's all calm down first.
Stay calm.
It's ringing, but no one's answering.
Oh my God!
What happened?
Brother Nanding! Brother Nanding!
Where is she?
What happened?
Sir!
MJ! Where's Chiara?
Ma'am, I don't know.
What’s happening?
Everyone's just guessing.
I'm already sweating my ass off here!
Is the wedding still happening?
Of course it is. After everything
that's happened, of course it is.
Oh, no.
Nanding! Oh my God! Oh my God!
Where is she?
Is our Internet connection
the only problem?
It looks like it's not, sir.
This doesn't look like
a simple connection problem.
Any update on that?
I'm calling Agent Alex,
but she's not answering.
Okay, hold on.
I'll check with Carlota too.
It's ringing, but no one's answering.
Mikoy.
Chiara is missing.
She's not in the bridal car either.
Are you sure?
Where's Chiara?
Maybe she just went to the bathroom.
Or maybe she forgot something
and went back to the hotel.
That's possible.
It's possible, but…
I'm going to find Chiara.
-Let's take a look.
-What's going on?
-Mikoy!
-Hey!
-Come--
-Mikoy!
Mikoy!
Thank you so, so much for this day.
Please guide us.
I know you won't abandon us.
You alone know what is meant to happen
and when the time is right.
What do you mean Chiara
is missing? What happened?
They said Chiara isn't in the bridal car.
They can't get ahold of the driver either.
They can't get ahold of the driver?
Wait.
What's going on, Carlota?
According to the wedding planner,
the driver was unconscious.
Everything scheduled
for each hour went as planned.
That is, until a few minutes
before the bridal march.
Oddly,
it took a while for the door to open.
before everyone started to worry.
I immediately followed the wedding planner
to personally check on Chiara.
At first, we thought the bridal car driver
was unconscious.
But it turned out
he had just fallen asleep.
He just fell asleep?
Could someone have made him fall asleep?
So we didn't let it go.
We interrogated him.
Nanding, it's impossible for you
to just fall asleep while you're at work.
I don't know either, ma'am.
I just suddenly fell asleep.
Nanding, what's the last thing
you remember before you fell asleep?
Ma'am, we arrived here,
and as soon as I got here,
I passed out. I fell asleep.
I don't remember what happened after that.
Did Chiara say anything
before you stopped here at the church?
No, sir.
She didn't say anything to me.
My head still hurts badly even now.
The bride wasn't coming
from that far away from the church.
So? Why did the driver fall asleep?
We checked his car, sir.
It looks like the smart car
scent diffuser was the trigger,
which caused him to fall asleep.
So how?
Did someone put sleeping agents
in the scent before the wedding?
If someone put the driver to sleep,
does that mean Chiara was kidnapped?
Chiara could have been
the one who sprayed it.
Why would she do that?
Could she have gotten cold feet
at the last minute
and wanted to run away?
that does happen.
That seems impossible.
After everything they've been through,
would she really have doubts now?
if she has an issue or a concern,
she'll tell you about it directly.
If she had any doubts before the wedding,
I'm sure she would've brought them up
with Mikoy so they could talk about it.
That's exactly what Mikoy said too, sir.
Even when their preparations
got stressful,
they were open and transparent
with each other.
And they made sure to discuss everything.
we know that she's the kind of person
who can make decisions and make moves
without telling anyone.
Chiara has a history of doing that.
But this is different.
This was supposed to be
her wedding to Mikoy.
This was something
they prepared for together.
It seems out of character for her
to suddenly make a move on her own.
We also talked to everyone
who interacted with Chiara.
From the glam team,
the person who made
her gown, the photographer,
all the hotel staff
who were on duty that morning.
Even all the guests who saw her.
None of them noticed anything unusual.
In fact, they all said the same thing.
That Chiara was a beautiful
and excited bride.
What time was the last time
you saw Chiara?
Actually, I was with her
about 30 minutes ago.
We even double-checked her dress.
Then I helped her into the car.
What did you notice about her mindset,
about how she was feeling?
Was she happy? Sad? Angry?
She was so happy,
really excited about her dress.
She was so excited.
I don't know, my goodness!
Did you leave her there,
or did she leave the place herself?
Once she got into the bridal car,
that was it.
-That was the last time we saw her.
-That was the last time you saw her.
How many minutes ago was that?
Aside from going to Mikoy's house,
we also checked the CCTV footage
from the church and the hotel.
But Chiara never returned to the hotel.
And she never got
out of the bridal car either.
Mario also helped us ask around for help.
In case they saw anything
or noticed anything unusual.
You don't have any leads
or anything from your informants?
I'm sorry, Mario,
but as of now, we can't say that
Chiara Valtrovi is a missing person.
That's because of the 24-hour window.
But a lot can happen within 24 hours.
We can't just sit around and do nothing.
With all due respect, Mario,
this could be a case of a runaway bride.
And besides, Mario,
it's no secret that the bride was once
part of the mafia.
Maybe, you know,
she went back to her old life.
It's not officially confirmed yet that
Chiara is a missing person.
What's important is,
all the police have been alerted
at every checkpoint
to watch out for Chiara.
We also spoke to Donabel and Viktor.
They spoke as a family
before Chiara left the hotel.
Papa Vik.
Mama Donabel.
How was your conversation with Chiara?
It was okay, Mikoy.
Just a brief catch-up.
Yes.
Our little reunion was cut short.
Did she mention anything
that was bothering her?
Or did you notice anything unusual
about her?
Nothing.
Chiara actually seemed so happy.
And she even said, didn't she, that
love is ultimately a decision.
So,
she was completely committed
to marrying you.
To spend the rest of her life with you.
Viktor, what happened to our daughter?
Where's Chiara now?
Viktor, during your brief conversation
with Chiara,
did she mention anything?
Did she mention anyone?
Anything at all.
A person, someone she knew, or an event.
Nothing, Agent Alex.
Chiara is missing.
I don’t know where to start.
But maybe you have to rest first.
But we’re wasting so much time!
I think Tess is right.
You better rest first.
Mom. Chiara might be in more danger
if we stop searching.
I have so many secrets to hide
just to give our family
a simple life, Mikoy.
Because of that, I feel like
fate is making me pay.
Only if you knew, it’s so hard
for me to see you suffer.
You’re a good person, my son.
And I will do everything just to help you.
Sean is talking to someone suspicious.
There’s a new character
in Chiara and Mikoy’s life.
And now she’s a running away bride?
This Vicky should be investigated.
Is there’s still no news
about my daughter?
For now, none.
Chiara is not someone
who will just disappear.
I think there’s something that happened.